[
    { "question": "กระดาษ", "answer": "paper"},
    { "question": "กระดูก", "answer": "bone"},
    { "question": "กระเบื้อง", "answer": "tile"},
    { "question": "กระเป๋า", "answer": "bag"},
    { "question": "กระเป๋าเสื้อ", "answer": "pocket"},
    { "question": "กระโปรง", "answer": "skirt"},
    { "question": "กลับ", "answer": "back"},
    { "question": "กล่อง", "answer": "box"},
    { "question": "กล้อง", "answer": "camera"},
    { "question": "กางเกง", "answer": "pants"},
    { "question": "การออกกำลังกาย", "answer": "exercise"},
    { "question": "การแต่งกาย", "answer": "dress"},
    { "question": "กีฬา", "answer": "sport"},
    { "question": "กุญแจ", "answer": "key"},
    { "question": "ขน", "answer": "fur"},
    { "question": "ขนตา", "answer": "eyelash"},
    { "question": "ขวา", "answer": "right"},
    { "question": "ของขวัญ", "answer": "gift"},
    { "question": "ขา", "answer": "leg"},
    { "question": "ขึ้น", "answer": "up"},
    { "question": "ข้าง", "answer": "beside"},
    { "question": "ข้างนอก", "answer": "outside"},
    { "question": "ข้างใน", "answer": "inside"},
    { "question": "ครัว", "answer": "kitchen"},
    { "question": "คลื่น", "answer": "wave"},
    { "question": "ความตาย", "answer": "death"},
    { "question": "ความร้อน", "answer": "heat"},
    { "question": "ความสงบสุข", "answer": "peace"},
    { "question": "ความเจ็บปวด", "answer": "pain"},
    { "question": "คอ", "answer": "neck"},
    { "question": "คำกริยา", "answer": "verb"},
    { "question": "คำคุณศัพท์", "answer": "adjective"},
    { "question": "คำนาม", "answer": "noun"},
    { "question": "คิ้ว", "answer": "eyebrow"},
    { "question": "คุก", "answer": "prison"},
    { "question": "ค่าย", "answer": "camp"},
    { "question": "ฆาตกรรม", "answer": "murder"},
    { "question": "งานแต่งงาน", "answer": "wedding"},
    { "question": "จดหมาย", "answer": "letter"},
    { "question": "จมูก", "answer": "nose"},
    { "question": "จังหวัด", "answer": "province"},
    { "question": "จุด", "answer": "dot"},
    { "question": "ชั้น", "answer": "floor"},
    { "question": "ชายหาด", "answer": "beach"},
    { "question": "ชิ้น", "answer": "piece"},
    { "question": "ซ้าย", "answer": "left"},
    { "question": "ดวงจันทร์", "answer": "moon"},
    { "question": "ดวงอาทิตย์", "answer": "sun"},
    { "question": "ดอกไม้", "answer": "flower"},
    { "question": "ดอลลาร์", "answer": "dollar"},
    { "question": "ดาว", "answer": "star"},
    { "question": "ดิน", "answer": "soil"},
    { "question": "ดินสอ", "answer": "pencil"},
    { "question": "ด้าน", "answer": "side"},
    { "question": "ด้านบน", "answer": "top"},
    { "question": "ด้านล่าง", "answer": "bottom"},
    { "question": "ด้านหน้า", "answer": "front"},
    { "question": "ด้านหลัง", "answer": "back"},
    { "question": "ตรง", "answer": "straight"},
    { "question": "ตลาด", "answer": "market"},
    { "question": "ตะวันตก", "answer": "west"},
    { "question": "ตะวันออก", "answer": "east"},
    { "question": "ตัวเมือง", "answer": "town"},
    { "question": "ตา", "answer": "eye"},
    { "question": "ตาราง", "answer": "table"},
    { "question": "ตำบล", "answer": "district"},
    { "question": "ติดตั้ง", "answer": "install"},
    { "question": "ต้นไม้", "answer": "tree"},
    { "question": "ถนน", "answer": "street"},
    { "question": "ถุงมือ", "answer": "gloves"},
    { "question": "ถุงเท้า", "answer": "socks"},
    { "question": "ถ่ายภาพ", "answer": "photograph"},
    { "question": "ทราย", "answer": "sand"},
    { "question": "ทะเล", "answer": "sea"},
    { "question": "ทะเลสาป", "answer": "lake"},
    { "question": "ทิศทาง", "answer": "direction"},
    { "question": "ทีม", "answer": "team"},
    { "question": "ที่", "answer": "at"},
    { "question": "ท้องฟ้า", "answer": "sky"},
    { "question": "ธนาคาร", "answer": "bank"},
    { "question": "ธรรมชาติ", "answer": "nature"},
    { "question": "นก", "answer": "bird"},
    { "question": "นาฬิกา", "answer": "clock"},
    { "question": "นิตยสาร", "answer": "magazine"},
    { "question": "นิ้ว", "answer": "finger"},
    { "question": "นิ้วเท้า", "answer": "toe"},
    { "question": "น้ำแข็ง", "answer": "ice"},
    { "question": "บัตร", "answer": "card"},
    { "question": "บันทึก", "answer": "note"},
    { "question": "บ้าน", "answer": "house"},
    { "question": "ประตู", "answer": "door"},
    { "question": "ประเทศ", "answer": "country"},
    { "question": "ประเทศชาติ", "answer": "nation"},
    { "question": "ปลา", "answer": "fish"},
    { "question": "ปลูก", "answer": "plant"},
    { "question": "ปาก", "answer": "mouth"},
    { "question": "ปากกา", "answer": "pen"},
    { "question": "ปีก", "answer": "wing"},
    { "question": "ปืน", "answer": "gun"},
    { "question": "ป่า", "answer": "forest"},
    { "question": "ผนัง", "answer": "wall"},
    { "question": "ผม", "answer": "hair"},
    { "question": "ผิว", "answer": "skin"},
    { "question": "ผ้าพันคอ", "answer": "scarf"},
    { "question": "ฝน", "answer": "rain"},
    { "question": "ฝัน", "answer": "dream"},
    { "question": "พยัญชนะ", "answer": "consonant"},
    { "question": "พลังงาน", "answer": "energy"},
    { "question": "พื้น", "answer": "ground"},
    { "question": "ฟัน", "answer": "tooth"},
    { "question": "ฟาร์ม", "answer": "farm"},
    { "question": "ภาพ", "answer": "image"},
    { "question": "ภูเขา", "answer": "mountain"},
    { "question": "มหาวิทยาลัย", "answer": "university"},
    { "question": "มหาสมุทร", "answer": "ocean"},
    { "question": "มือ", "answer": "hand"},
    { "question": "ม้า", "answer": "horse"},
    { "question": "ยา", "answer": "drug"},
    { "question": "ยา", "answer": "medicine"},
    { "question": "ยาพิษ", "answer": "poison"},
    { "question": "รองเท้า", "answer": "shoes"},
    { "question": "รัฐ", "answer": "state"},
    { "question": "ราก", "answer": "root"},
    { "question": "ราคา", "answer": "price"},
    { "question": "ริมฝีปาก", "answer": "lips"},
    { "question": "รู", "answer": "hole"},
    { "question": "ร่างกายมนุษย์", "answer": "human body"},
    { "question": "ร้านค้า / ร้านค้า", "answer": "store/shop"},
    { "question": "ร้านอาหาร", "answer": "restaurant"},
    { "question": "ลง", "answer": "down"},
    { "question": "ลม", "answer": "wind"},
    { "question": "ลวดลาย", "answer": "pattern"},
    { "question": "ลาน", "answer": "yard"},
    { "question": "ลิ้น", "answer": "tongue"},
    { "question": "ลูกบอล", "answer": "ball"},
    { "question": "ล็อค", "answer": "lock"},
    { "question": "วัด", "answer": "temple"},
    { "question": "วัว", "answer": "cow"},
    { "question": "วิทยาศาสตร์", "answer": "science"},
    { "question": "วิทยุ", "answer": "radio"},
    { "question": "ศาล", "answer": "court"},
    { "question": "ศาสนา", "answer": "religion"},
    { "question": "สงคราม", "answer": "war"},
    { "question": "สถานที่", "answer": "location"},
    { "question": "สถานีรถไฟ", "answer": "train station"},
    { "question": "สนามบิน", "answer": "airport"},
    { "question": "สบู่", "answer": "soap"},
    { "question": "สมอง", "answer": "brain"},
    { "question": "สระ", "answer": "pool"},
    { "question": "สระ", "answer": "vowel"},
    { "question": "สวน", "answer": "garden"},
    { "question": "สวน", "answer": "park"},
    { "question": "สะพาน", "answer": "bridge"},
    { "question": "สัญญา", "answer": "contract"},
    { "question": "สัญญาณ", "answer": "sign"},
    { "question": "สัตว์", "answer": "animal"},
    { "question": "สำนักงาน", "answer": "office"},
    { "question": "สี", "answer": "paint"},
    { "question": "สูท", "answer": "suit"},
    { "question": "หญ้า", "answer": "grass"},
    { "question": "หนังสือ", "answer": "book"},
    { "question": "หนังสือพิมพ์", "answer": "newspaper"},
    { "question": "หนู", "answer": "rat"},
    { "question": "หน้า", "answer": "page"},
    { "question": "หน้าจอ", "answer": "screen"},
    { "question": "หน้าต่าง", "answer": "window"},
    { "question": "หมวก", "answer": "hat"},
    { "question": "หมา", "answer": "dog"},
    { "question": "หมู", "answer": "pig"},
    { "question": "หยดน้ำตา", "answer": "teardrop"},
    { "question": "หลังคา", "answer": "roof"},
    { "question": "หัว", "answer": "head"},
    { "question": "หัวใจ", "answer": "heart"},
    { "question": "หิมะ", "answer": "snow"},
    { "question": "หุบเขา", "answer": "valley"},
    { "question": "หู", "answer": "ear"},
    { "question": "ห้อง", "answer": "room"},
    { "question": "ห้องนอน", "answer": "bedroom"},
    { "question": "ห้องสมุด", "answer": "library"},
    { "question": "ห้องอาบน้ำ", "answer": "bathroom"},
    { "question": "อพาร์ทเม้น", "answer": "apartment"},
    { "question": "อากาศ", "answer": "air"},
    { "question": "อาคาร", "answer": "building"},
    { "question": "อิฐ", "answer": "brick"},
    { "question": "เกม", "answer": "game"},
    { "question": "เกาะ", "answer": "island"},
    { "question": "เก้าอี้", "answer": "chair"},
    { "question": "เข็ม", "answer": "needle"},
    { "question": "เข่า", "answer": "knee"},
    { "question": "เครา", "answer": "beard"},
    { "question": "เครือข่าย", "answer": "network"},
    { "question": "เครื่องมือ", "answer": "tool"},
    { "question": "เงิน", "answer": "money"},
    { "question": "เตียง", "answer": "bed"},
    { "question": "เท้า", "answer": "foot"},
    { "question": "เนินเขา", "answer": "hill"},
    { "question": "เนื้อไม้", "answer": "wood"},
    { "question": "เบา", "answer": "light"},
    { "question": "เพดาน", "answer": "ceiling"},
    { "question": "เพศ", "answer": "gender"},
    { "question": "เมือง", "answer": "city"},
    { "question": "เม้าส์", "answer": "mouse"},
    { "question": "เลือด", "answer": "blood"},
    { "question": "เล็บมือ", "answer": "fingernail"},
    { "question": "เสียง", "answer": "sound"},
    { "question": "เสียงพูด", "answer": "voice"},
    { "question": "เสื้อผ้า", "answer": "clothing"},
    { "question": "เสื้อยืดคอกลม", "answer": "T-shirt"},
    { "question": "เสื้อเชิ้ต", "answer": "shirt"},
    { "question": "เสื้อโค้ท", "answer": "coat"},
    { "question": "เหงื่อ", "answer": "sweat"},
    { "question": "เหนือ", "answer": "north"},
    { "question": "แกะ", "answer": "sheep"},
    { "question": "แขน", "answer": "arm"},
    { "question": "แต่งงาน", "answer": "marriage"},
    { "question": "แผนที่", "answer": "map"},
    { "question": "แพะ", "answer": "goat"},
    { "question": "แมว", "answer": "cat"},
    { "question": "แม่น้ำ", "answer": "river"},
    { "question": "แหวน", "answer": "ring"},
    { "question": "โคมไฟ", "answer": "lamp"},
    { "question": "โจมตี", "answer": "attack"},
    { "question": "โทรทัศน์", "answer": "television"},
    { "question": "โทรศัพท์", "answer": "telephone"},
    { "question": "มือถือ", "answer": "cell phone"},
    { "question": "โบสถ์", "answer": "church"},
    { "question": "โรค", "answer": "disease"},
    { "question": "โรงพยาบาล", "answer": "hospital"},
    { "question": "โรงละคร", "answer": "theater"},
    { "question": "โรงเรียน", "answer": "school"},
    { "question": "โรงแรม", "answer": "hotel"},
    { "question": "โลก", "answer": "Earth" },
    { "question": "ใต้", "answer": "south"},
    { "question": "ใบหน้า", "answer": "face"},
    { "question": "ใบไม้", "answer": "leaf"},
    { "question": "ได้รับบาดเจ็บ", "answer": "injury"},
    { "question": "ไฟ", "answer": "fire"},
    { "question": "ไหล่", "answer": "shoulder"}
]
